Kheel Center AV Collection 6118 AV
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- Robert McKersie: Festschrift, October 30-31, 1998, 19 (Box 18)
  #283
- The Fight of Our Lives!, 20 (Box 18)
  #289
- Crafted With Pride in USA: Public Relations Campaign, November 1, 1984, 21 (Box 18)
- LMP Road to Results, 2003; 22 (Box 18)
  part one, part two -- December 2003
- Labor Management Partnership: Power of Partnership: Changing Our Jobs and Power of Partnership: the Genesis, 2002; 23 (Box 18)
  September 9, 2002
- The Power of Partnership: Changing our jobs (video one); The Genesis (bonus video), 24 (Box 18)
- Blueprint for Battle (collection /4283 AV-box 96), 10 (Box 20)
  and cover
- Lawrence, Massachusetts Textile Strike - (collection #/4283 AV - Box 96), 9 (Box 20)
- Text accompanying LP's in folders 9&10 (collection #/4283 AV/bx 96), 8 (Box 20)
- Unemployment Compensation Blues/Chins Up by Joe Glazer, 1 (Box 20)
  #462
- Labor's Challenge - Story of Organized Labor in the United States, 2 (Box 20)
- Slave Labor Camp Songs of the USSR - May 7, 1952, 3 (Box 20)
  10-1/2" reel and transcripts
- The Peoples Platform - March 3, 1945 (part two), 4 (Box 20)
  #484 -- Central NY Broadcasting Corp., Starrett-Syracuse Bld., Syracuse, NY -- removed from box 307, which was deleted from collection
- [Label lost]: (ca.1943?), 5 (Box 20)
  #486 -- Central NY Broadcasting Corp., Starrett Syracuse Bld., Syracuse, NY -- removed from box 307, which was deleted from collection
- I.L.G.W.U. Chorus Part 1 - 6/18/1947 (?) label can not be read. - 6036/092 AV - home collection, 6 (Box 20)
  part 1 - 33-1/3 RPM, start at inside for listening - 16" LP
- I.L.G.W.U. Chorus - 6/18/1947 - [6036/092 AV is home collection], 7 (Box 20)
  Part 2 - start from inside - 33-1/3 RPM - 16" disc --
- JFK Last Words to Labor (Box 84)
  - JFK Last Words to Labor (Box 84)
    12-1/2" reel
- Conversation at the White House (Box 85.1)
  - Conversation at the White House [85.1] (Box 85.1)
- Conversation at the White House (Box 85.2)
  - Conversation at the White House (Box 85.2)
- Conversation at the White House (Box 85.3)
  - Conversation at the White House (Box 85.3)
- UTU Convention One (Box 86.1)
  - UTU Convention One [86.1] (Box 86.1)
- UTU Convention One (Box 86.2)
  - UTU Convention One (Box 86.2)
- Railroad Man (Box 87.1)
  - Railroad Man [87.1] (Box 87.1)
    12-1/2" reels
- Railroad Man (Box 87.2)
  - Railroad Man (Box 87.2)
- Chicago Report (Box 89.1)
  - Chicago Report [89.1] (Box 89.1)
- Chicago Report (Box 89.2)
  - Chicago Report (Box 89.2)
- Chicago Report (Box 89.3)
  - Chicago Report (Box 89.3)
- Series 2 C1 (Box 90.1)
- Working on the railroad Series 8 C1 (Box 90.11)
- Working on the Railroad Series 7 C1 (Box 90.12)
- Working on the Railroad Series 7 C2 (Box 90.13)
- Working on the Railroad Series 5, c.2 (Box 90.14)
- Working on the Railroad Series 6, C1 (Box 90.15)
- Working on the Railroad Series 4 C2 (Box 90.16)
- Working on the Railroad Series 4 C1 (Box 90.17)
- Working on the Railroad Series 1 C1 (Box 90.18)
- Working on the Railroad Series 1 C2 (Box 90.19)
- Series 5 C1 (Box 90.2)
- Series 1 C3 (Box 90.3)
  - Working on the Railroads (Box 90)
    "Working on the Railroads." Railway Labor Executive Board. Norman Paige, H.E. Gilbert, and Senator Vance Hartke on interview. re: Hartke Resolution to investigate railroad finances and the poverty myth -- Series 7 (3 copies); Series 6 (2 copies); Series 5 (2 copies); Series 4 (2 copies); Series 1 (5 copies); Series 3; Series 2; Series 8
- Series 1 C4 (Box 90.4)
- Series 1 C5 (Box 90.5)
- Series 6 C3 (Box 90.6)
- Series 7 C3 (Box 90.7)
- Series 6 C2 (Box 90.8)
- Series 3 C1 (Box 90.9)
- Moving On, c.1 (Box 91.1)
  - Movin On (Box 91)
    3 copies
- Moving On, roll #1, C.2 (Box 91.2)
- Moving On, roll#2, c.2 (Box 91.3)
- I Visited the Burlington Shop (Box 92)
  - I Visited the Burlington Shop (Box 92)
    "I Visited the Burlington Shop". International Brotherhood of Machinists. Burlington, Iowa. Diesel shop film describing the machinist work on diesel locomotives. -- 15" reel
- And Women Must Weep (Box 93)
  - And Women Must Weep (Box 93)
    National Right to Work Committee. "And Women Must Weep." 1958 (25 mins) based on the events during a strike by International Association of Machinists Local 1459 of Princeton, Indiana, attempts to show that compulsory unionism denies not only the right to work, but the right of rank and file members to disagree with the ruling body of a "union shop" union. The film prompted the IAM to produce "ANATOMY OF A LIE" which attempts to discredit the charges in this film, AND WOMEN MUST WEEP. -- 10-1/2" reel
- Anatomy of a Lie (Box 94)
  - Anatomy of a Lie: #94 (Box 94)
    International Association of Machinists. "Anatomy of a Lie" 1961 (25 mins) A Pro-Union production attempts to discredit charges in the National Right to Work Film, AND WOMEN MUST WEEP. The IAM challenges the honesty of WOMEN on several points: the participation of Mrs. Ruth Munroe, president of Local 1459 (IAM), the size of the group taking the strike period immediately following the production of the two films, the WOMEN film becomes something of a standard tool in anti-union campaigns and the LIE film was used by unions to refute the charges made in the WOMEN film. -10" reel in 12-1/2" can
- Patton- Republic Steel (Box 95)
  - Mr. Patton on Steel Strike - Republic Steel: #95 (Box 95)
    A Wilding Production, 20 min. - 10-1/2" reel
- Cope Wallace (Box 96)
  - When Wallace got the vote: with a statement by Al H. Chesser, Pres. U.T.U.: #96 (Box 96)
    6 min. 24 sec., 16 mm, color; Note to projectionist: At end of Wallace film (Title: Phoenix Films, Inc.) Re-Focus and adjust sound level -- (info. taken off can cover) - 7" reel
- Steam Engine (Box 97)
  - Steam Engine: #97 (Box 97)
    8mm - job no. 16119 - date rec'd. 2/10/1948 (info taken off can) - 7" reel
- Kefauver on RR Mergers (Box 100)
  - Kefauver on RR Mergers: #100 (Box 100)
    2 films/1 box - 2-1/2" films
- Americans at Work Series 1-3 (Box 102)
- Americans at Work Series 1 (Box 102.1)
  - Americans at Work Series 1-3 (Box 102)
    2 copies -- 9-1/2" reel
- Americans at Work Series 2 (Box 102.2)
- Americans at Work Series 3 (Box 102.3)
- Leighty at Press Club (Box 103)
  - Leighty at Press Club (Box 103)
    12-1/2" film reel
- LBJ at the AFL-CIO Convention (Box 104)
  - LBJ at the AFL-CIO Convention (Box 104)
    Producer: Telenews -- 20:26 minutes -- Capital Film Laboratories, Incorporated -- 10-1/2" reel
- Two Miles a Minute (Box 112)
  - Two Miles a Minute (Box 112)
    7" reel
- On the Move (Box 113)
  - On the Move (Box 113)
    10-1/2" reel film
- Testimony - Justice v. JP Stevens (Box 146.1)
  - Testimony - Justice v. JP Stevens [146.1] (Box 146)
    14" film
- Testimony - Justice v. JP Stevens (Box 146.2)
  - Testimony - Justice v. JP Stevens (Box 146.2)
    14-1/2" film
- Testimony - Justice v. JP Stevens (Box 146.3)
  - Testimony - Justice v. JP Stevens (Box 146.3)
- Testimony - Justice v. JP Stevens (Box 146.4)
  - Testimony - Justice v. JP Stevens (Box 146.4)
- Testimony - Justice v. JP Stevens (Box 146.5)
  - Testimony - Justice v. JP Stevens (Box 146.5)
- Testimony - Justice v. JP Stevens (Box 146.6)
  - Testimony - Justice v. JP Stevens (Box 146.6)
- "24 Hours in Tyrantland" Jane Wyatt (Box 241)
  - AV 241 (Box 241)
- "COPE" (Box 242)
  - "COPE" (Box 242)
    10-1/2" reel - #242
- Whitney's Convention 1946 (Box 243)
  - Whitney's Convention 1946 (Box 243)
    7-1/2" reel -- #243
- Look for the Union Label (Box 244)
  - Look for the Union Label (Box 244)
    10-1/2" reel -- #244
- Like a Beautiful Child (Box 245)
  - Like a Beautiful Child - #132 (Box 245)
- I Am Somebody (Box 246)
  - I Am Somebody: #131 (Box 246)
    12-1/2" reel - #246
- Hospital Strike - Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Employees. National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, Local 1199. (Box 247)
  - Hospital Strike - Retail, Wholesale, and Department Store Employees. National Union of Hospital and Health Care Employees, Local 1199. (Box 247)
    was #133 - 12-1/2" reel
- The Copper Strike (Box 248)
  - The Copper Strike (Box 248)
- Triangle Fire - PBS - c.2 (Box 249)
  - Triangle Fire - PBS - c.2 (Box 249)
- Triangle Fire - PBS - c.3 (Box 250)
  - Triangle Fire - PBS - c.3 (Box 250)
- In the shadow of the tower -- listed on finding aid as #417 (Box 251)
  - In the shadow of the tower (Box 251)
    listed on finding aid as #417 -- removed from box 15
- In the shadow of the tower -- listed on finding aid as #417 (Box 252)
  - In the shadow of the tower (Box 252)
    listed on finding aid as #417 -- removed from bx 15
- In the shadow of the tower (Box 253)
  - In the shadow of the tower (Box 253)
    Master -- removed from bx 13
- In the shadow of the tower (Box 254)
  - In the shadow of the tower (Box 254)
    Duplication Master -- removed from bx 13
- In the shadow of the tower (Box 255)
  - In the shadow of the tower (Box 255)
    removed from bx 13
- In the shadow of the tower (Box 256)
  - In the shadow of the tower (Box 256)
- In the shadow of the tower - moved to the library collection - call no. LD1346.75. I5 1992 (Box 257)
  - In the shadow of the tower (Box 257)
- Welcome to labor land: Bucky Halker and the complete unknowns -- listed on the finding aid as #380 (Box 258)
  - Welcome to labor land: Bucky Halker and the complete unknowns (Box 258)
    listed on the finding aid as #380 -- removed from bx 15
- Willaim Bates: The living heart of New York City -- listed on finding aid as #439 (Box 259)
  - William Bates: The living heart of New York City (Box 259)
    listed on finding aid as #439 -- removed from bx 15 -- not cataloged
- Emma Goldman: An exceedingly dangerous woman -- listed on finding aid as #440 (Box 260)
  - Emma Goldman: An exceedingly dangerous woman (Box 260)
    listed on finding aid as #440 -- removed from bx 15
- Young and younger / George Mann, Julius Margolin (Box 261)
  - Young and younger / George Mann, Julius Margolin (Box 261)
    removed from bx 11 -- [#368 on finding aid]
- Pierre Fournier: De lutte en turlautte (Box 262)
  - Pierre Fournier: De lutte en turlautte (Box 262)
    removed from bx 11 -- [#363 on finding aid]
- Anne Feeney: have you been to Jail for Justice? (Box 263)
  - Anne Feeney: have you been to Jail for Justice? (Box 263)
    removed from bx 11 -- [#362 on finding aid]
- Solidarity: it can't be beat (Box 264)
  - Solidarity: it can't be beat (Box 264)
    removed from bx 11 -- [#374 on finding aid]
- Workers rise: Labor in the spotlight/New York City Labor Chorus (Box 265)
  - Workers rise: Labor in the spotlight/New York City Labor Chorus (Box 265)
    removed from bx 11 -- [#327 (c.3) on finding aid]
- Workers rise: Labor in the spotlight/New York City Labor Chorus (Box 266)
  - Workers rise: Labor in the spotlight/New York City Labor Chorus (Box 266)
    removed from bx 11 -- [#327 (c.1) on finding aid]
- Workers Rise: labor in the spotlight/New York City Labor Chorus (Box 267)
  - Workers Rise: labor in the spotlight/New York City Labor Chorus (Box 267)
    removed from bx 11 -- [#327 (c.2) on finding aid]
- Pins and needles (Box 268)
  - Pins and needles: removed from bx 11 (Box 268)
    [#166 on finding aid]
- We ain't gonna give it back: songs for the labor movement/John O'Connor (Box 269)
  - We ain't gonna give it back: songs for the labor movement/John O'Connor (Box 269)
    removed from bx 11 -- [#203 on finding aid]
- The Songs of Pete Seeger: vol. 2 (Box 270)
  - The Songs of Pete Seeger: vol. 2 (Box 270)
    removed from bx 11 -- [#377 on finding aid]
- Kirk Kelly: New city (Box 271)
  - Kirk Kelly: New city (Box 271)
    removed from bx 11 -- [#367 on finding aid]
- General Strike: Fanning the flames of discontent (Box 272)
  - General Strike: Fanning the flames of discontent (Box 272)
    removed from bx 11 -- [#365 on finding aid]
- Pat Humphries hands (Box 273)
  - Pat Humphries hands (Box 273)
    removed from bx 11 -- [#366 on finding aid]
- Paul Robeson: the peace arch concerts (Box 274)
  - Paul Robeson: the peace arch concerts (Box 274)
    removed from bx 11 -- [#372 on finding aid]
- Two roads: 28 years, Joe Uehlein (Box 275)
  - Two roads: 28 years, Joe Uehlein (Box 275)
    removed from bx 11 -- [#375 on finding aid]
- General Strike: Fanning the flames of discontent (Box 276)
  - General Strike: Fanning the flames of discontent (Box 276)
- John L. Handcox (Box 277)
  - John L. Handcox (Box 277)
    removed from bx 11 -- [#381 on finding aid]
- A Bridge between two worlds (Box 278)
  - A Bridge between two worlds (Box 278)
    removed from bx 11 -- [#391 on finding aid]
- Canciones por la causa (Box 279)
  - Canciones por la causa (Box 279)
    removed from bx 11 -- [#376 on finding aid]
- Stand Up together (Box 280)
  - Stand Up together (Box 280)
    removed from bx 11 -- [#369 on finding aid]
- Pam Parker & Co.: Working Class (Box 281)
  - Pam Parker & Co.: Working Class (Box 281)
    removed from bx 11 -- [#370 on finding aid]
- Solidarity Rocks (Box 282)
  - Solidarity Rocks (Box 282)
    removed from bx 11 -- [#373 on finding aid]
- Phil Cohen & Patricia Ford: Caution to the wind (Box 283)
  - Phil Cohen & Patricia Ford: Caution to the wind (Box 283)
    removed from bx 11 -- [#361 on finding aid]
- Jon Fromer - We do the work (Box 284)
  - Jon Fromer - We do the work (Box 284)
    removed from bx 11 -- [#364 on finding aid]
- til we outnumber 'em (Box 285)
  - 'til we outnumber 'em (Box 285)
    removed from bx 11 -- [#378 on finding aid]
- Rebel Voices (Box 286)
  - Rebel Voices (Box 286)
    removed from box 11 [#371 on finding aid]
- Blackjack David, Dave Alvin (Box 287)
  - Rebel Voices (Box 287)
- Schmatta from TV (Box 288)
  - Schmatta from TV (Box 288)
    removed from bx 21 -- [#463 on finding aid]
- At home in Utopia (Box 289)
  - At home in Utopia (Box 289)
    removed from bx 21 -- [#398 on finding aid]
- Schmatta from TV (Box 290)
  - Schmatta from TV (Box 290)
- Schmatta from TV (Box 291)
  - Schmatta from TV (Box 291)
- The Philosopher Kings (Box 292)
  - The Philosopher Kings (Box 292)
    removed from bx 21 -- [#399 on finding aid]
- O bittre zeit: Lagerlieder: 1933 bis 1945: Liedorte (2) (Box 293.1)
  - O bittre zeit: Lagerlieder: 1933 bis 1945: Liedvariationen (3) (Box 293)
    removed from bx 21 -- [#396 on finding aid]
  - O bittre zeit: Lagerlieder: 1933 bis 1945: Liedorte (2) (Box 293)
  - O bittre zeit: Lagerlieder: 1933 bis 1945: Liedzeugen O bittre zeit: Lagerlieder: 1933 bis 1945: Liedzeugen - (1) (Box 293)
    removed from bx 21 -- [#396 on finding aid] -- information booklets from CDs are in Accession folder
- O bittre zeit: Lagerlieder: 1933 bis 1945: Liedvariationen (3) (Box 293.2)
- O bittre zeit: Lagerlieder: 1933 bis 1945: Liedzeugen (1) (Box 293.3)
- Union Days 2007: Panel Discussion: April 5, 2007 (Box 294)
  - Union Days 2007: Panel Discussion: April 5, 2007 (Box 294)
    removed from bx 14 -- [#403 item no. on finding aid]
- Union Days 2007 - Keynote: Nancy Wolforth: April 4, 2007 (Box 295)
  - Union Days 2007 - Keynote: Nancy Wolforth: April 4, 2007 (Box 295)
    removed from bx 14 -- [#404 item no. on finding aid]
- Paula England: Alice Cook Lecture: April 6, 2006 (Box 296)
  - Paula England: Alice Cook Lecture: April 6, 2006 (Box 296)
    removed from bx 14 -- [#407 item no. on finding aid]
- Union Days 2006: Baldmear Velasquez: April 5, 2006 (Box 297)
  - Union Days 2006: Baldmear Velasquez: April 5, 2006 (Box 297)
    removed from bx 14 -- [#408 item no. on finding aid]
- Union Days Panel: April 7, 2006 (Box 298)
  - Union Days Panel: April 7, 2006 (Box 298)
    removed from bx 14 -- [#409 item no. on finding aid]
- Baldemar Velasquez & Friends: April 6, 2006 (Box 299)
  - Baldemar Velasquez & Friends: April 6, 2006 (Box 299)
    removed from box 14 -- [#410 item no. on finding aid
- Where do you stand?: Stories from an American mill (Box 300.1)
- Where do you stand?: Stories from an American mill (Box 300.2)
  - Where do you stand?: Stories from an American mill (Box 300)
    removed from bx 14 -- [#383 item no. on finding aid] -- 2 copies
- Locked Out: a David and Goliath stryggle between workers and a multi national coporation (Box 301)
  - Locked Out: a David and Goliath struggle between workers and a multi national corporation (Box 301)
- The Metropolis - two disc - Special edition (Box 302.1)
- The Metropolis - two disc - Special edition (Box 302.2)
  - The Metropolis - two disc - Special edition (Box 302)
- North & South -- two disc (Box 303.1)
- North & South -- two disc (Box 303.2)
  - North & South: two disc (Box 303)
- Time Capsule of 1904: Westinghouse Plants and People (Box 304)
  - Time Capsule of 1904: Westinghouse Plants and People (Box 304)
    removed from cassette file cabinet -- [#291 on finding aid]
- Whiteville Choir: UNITE! Local 1077: Union Power (Box 305)
  - Whiteville Choir: UNITE! Local 1077: Union Power (Box 305)
    [moved from cassette cabinet, collection 6000 AV, item 4] see finding aid
- Severt Speech: concerning livelihood of Crestline, Ohio pt. 1, 1 (Box 306)
  #469
- Near end of Severt's: Speech concerning livelihood of Crestline pt. II, 2 (Box 306)
- All but 3 mins. Of Severt's Speech, pt. III, 3 (Box 306)
- Levine Presentation - (2 of 2), 4 (Box 306)
  #468
- Beginning of the Levine Speech - National Manpower Speech: 5/4/1967, 5 (Box 306)
  #467
- Levine Presentation: vocational schools -- Q/A sessions - (1 of 2), 6 (Box 306)
- WSPD-TV "For the Record": Sun. @ 2 p.m.; w/T.J. McCormick, Toledo Area Council of RR Workers (Union Representatives), 7 (Box 306)
  #470
- Brandeis Program - 10/7/1966: WEVD Radio Program -- interview by Neuman, Baldwin and Hallard -- interviewee - Senator Kenneth Keating, 8 (Box 306)
  #466
- Saul Alinsky: home chat with kids about school; woman singing with piano, 9 (Box 306)
  #465
- Economic Issues in American Democracy: the Role of Unions in the American Economy / Teaching Resources Films, 10 (Box 306)
- Yamamba Act II, 11 (Box 306)
- A. Philip Randolph: For Jobs and Freedom, 12 (Box 306)
- A. Philip Randolph: For Jobs and Freedom, 13 (Box 306)
- A. Philip Randolph: For Jobs and Freedom, 14 (Box 306)
- A. Philip Randolph: For Jobs and Freedom, 15 (Box 306)
- A. Philip Randolph: For Jobs and Freedom, 16 (Box 306)
- Interview of Eric Trist by William Fox; Feb. 25, 1988, 17 (Box 306)
- Louise Coulton interviewed by Thomas Tyson, Oct. 8, 1991, 18 (Box 306)
- A Stitch in Time - 9/15/1995: tape 1, 19 (Box 306)
- A Stitch in Time - 9/15/1995: tape 2, 20 (Box 306)
- A Stitch in Time - 9/15/1995: tape 3, 21 (Box 306)
- Alumni Presentation - 6/1990, 22 (Box 306)
- Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives: Bernard J. Woolis Memorial Tribute: October 7, 1995, 23 (Box 306)
- In the Shadow of the Tower @ UAW Local 2300: #386, 1992; 24 (Box 306)
  1992 -- Use Copy
- Unusual and Blessed Destiny: a sample of a work in progress on the Life of Mary Van Kleeck, 1883-1973, 25 (Box 306)
- My Darling Party Line by Joe Glazer - #118 (Box 308)
  - My Darling Party Line by Joe Glazer (Box 308)
    #118
- Rising Again by Tom Juravich - #130 (Box 309.1)
  - Rising Again by Tom Juravich (Box 309)
    #130 (3 copies)
- Rising Again by Tom Juravich - #130 (Box 309.2)
- Rising Again by Tom Juravich - #130 (Box 309.3)
- Sing a Song by Tom Juravich - #140 (Box 310.1)
  - Sing a Song by Tom Juravich (Box 310)
    #140 (2 copies)
- Sing a Song by Tom Juravich - #140 (Box 310.2)
- Carry it on by Pete Seeger, Jane Sapp and Si Kahn - #143 (2 copies) (Box 311)
  - Carry it on by Pete Seeger, Jane Sapp and Si Kahn (Box 311)
    #143 (2 copies)
- Shays' Rebellion "Daniel Shays Highway" - #144 (Box 312)
  - Shays' Rebellion "Daniel Shays Highway" (Box 312)
    #144
- Justice in America - #151 (Box 313)
  - Justice in America (Box 313)
    #151
- Lifeline Still on Fire - #152 (2 copies) (Box 314)
  - Lifeline Still on Fire (Box 314)
    #152 (2 copies)
- Favorite American Union Songs by Tom Glazer - #164 (Box 315)
  - Favorite American Union Songs by Tom Glazer (Box 315)
    #164
- Pins and Needles - #166 (Master Copy) (Box 316)
  - Pins and Needles (Box 316)
    #166 (Master Copy)
- We Ain't Gonna Give It Back by John O'Connor - #203 (Box 317.1)
  - We Ain't Gonna Give It Back by John O'Connor (Box 317)
    #203 (2 copies)
- We Ain't Gonna Give It Back by John O'Connor - #203 (Box 317.2)
- A World to Win by Tom Juravich - #205 (2 copies) (Box 318)
  - A World to Win by Tom Juravich (Box 318)
    #205 (2 copies)
- In Solidarity by Arlene Mantle - #206 (Box 319.1)
  - In Solidarity by Arlene Mantle (Box 319)
    #206 (3 copies)
- In Solidarity by Arlene Mantle - #206 (Box 319.2)
- The UAW - Fifty Years in Song and Story with Joe Glazer - #207 (Box 320)
  - The UAW - Fifty Years in Song and Story with Joe Glazer (Box 320)
    #207
- The Triangle Fire by Leon Stein- #208 (Box 321)
  - The Triangle Fire by Leon Stein (Box 321)
    #208
- Still Singing Solidarity Forever! UPIU Local 20 - #210 (Box 322)
  - Still Singing Solidarity Forever! UPIU Local 20 (Box 322)
    #210
- Blue Collar Bluegrass with Kenny Winfree - #211 (Box 323.1)
  - Still Singing Solidarity Forever! UPIU Local 20 (Box 323)
- Blue Collar Bluegrass with Kenny Winfree - #211 (Box 323.2)
- AYA! A benefit tape for AIDS Vancouver - #212 (Box 324)
  - AYA! A benefit tape for AIDS Vancouver (Box 324)
    #212
- The Face on the Dime by Lee Hunter - #214 (Box 325)
  - The Face on the Dime by Lee Hunter (Box 325)
    #214
- Women's Work by Linda Allen - #215 (Box 326)
  - Women's Work by Linda Allen (Box 326)
    #215
- I have seen freedom by Si Kahn - #216 (Box 327)
  - I have seen freedom by Si Kahn (Box 327)
    #216
- I'll Be There by Si Kahn - #217 (Box 328)
  - I'll Be There by Si Kahn (Box 328)
- Some Sweet Day - The Musical by Si Kahn - #218 (Box 329)
  - Some Sweet Day - The Musical by Si Kahn (Box 329)
    #218
- Joe Glazer Labor Song's - #115 (Box 330)
  - Joe Glazer Labor Song's (Box 330)
    #115
- Tree of Life Guy Carawan, Arbol de la Vida with Candie Carawan & Friends - #219 (Box 331)
  - Tree of Life Guy Carawan, Arbol de la Vida with Candie Carawan & Friends (Box 331)
    #219
- Anne Romaine Take a Stand - #220 (Box 332)
  - Anne Romaine Take a Stand (Box 332)
    #220
- Anne Romaine While There is a Soul in Prison, I Am Not Free - #221 (Box 333)
  - Anne Romaine While There is a Soul in Prison, I Am Not Free (Box 333)
    #221
- Charlie King Two Good Arms - #222 (Box 334)
  - Charlie King Two Good Arms (Box 334)
    #222
- Sing For Freedom: the Story of the Civil Rights Movement Through it's Songs - #223 (Box 335)
  - Sing For Freedom: the Story of the Civil Rights Movement Through it's Songs (Box 335)
    #223
- Birth of 1199: The Drug Store Years - #224 (Box 336.1)
  - Birth of 1199: The Drug Store Years (Box 336)
    #224 (2 copies)
- Birth of 1199: The Drug Store Years - #224 (Box 336.2)
- Rebel Voices - #225 (Box 337)
  - Rebel Voices (Box 337)
    #225
- We Just Come to Work Here. We Don't Come to Die - #226 (Box 338)
  - We Just Come to Work Here. We Don't Come to Die (Box 338)
    #226
- Links On the Chain - #227 (Box 339)
  - Links On the Chain (Box 339)
    #227
- Songs for Labor by Jon Fromer - #228 (Box 340)
  - Songs for Labor by Jon Fromer (Box 340)
    #228
- Rockin' Solidarity Forever - #229 (Box 341)
  - Rockin' Solidarity Forever (Box 341)
    #229
- Finland Station - #230 (Box 342)
  - Finland Station (Box 342)
    #230
- This Line is Singin'! Picket Line Songs by the Freedom Song Network - #231 (Box 343)
  - This Line is Singin'! Picket Line Songs by the Freedom Song Network (Box 343)
    #231
- United We Bargain, Divided We Beg! - Anne Feeney and Friends - #232 (Box 344)
  - United We Bargain, Divided We Beg! - Anne Feeney and Friends (Box 344)
    #232
- There's a Whole Lot More of Us Than They Think - Anne Feeney and Friends - #233 (Box 345)